http://www.atto.com/privacy-policy

Toggle navigation
Products
XstreamCORE® Storage ConnectivityXstreamCORE® intelligent BridgesXstreamCORE® JBOF ControllersSiliconDisk™ RAM-based Storage ApplianceEthernet NICsFibre Channel HBAsSAS/SATA HBAsThunderbolt™ AdaptersSoftwareXtend SAN iSCSI InitiatorDisk Benchmark for WindowsDisk Benchmark for macOS®ATTO 360 Tuning Software
ATTO Exclusive TechnologiesAdaptive Path OptimizationAdvanced Data Streaming™ATTO ConfigTool™ATTO XstreamVIEW™CacheAssure™DriveAssure™eCORE™ Control Engineintelligent Bridging Architecture™MultiPath Director™vConfigTool™xCORE™ Data Acceleration
Solutions
How to Buy
Find a Reseller United States Canada Europe, Middle East & Africa Asia / Pacific South America & Latin America
Become a Reseller
Find a Distributor United States Canada Europe, Middle East & Africa Asia / Pacific South America & Latin America
Buy Direct (ATTO Store)
Partners
Support
Sales Support Contact ATTO SalesWarranty InformationRegister a ProductAuthorize SoftwareRe-Authorize SoftwareCable FinderDiscontinued Products
Technical SupportDownloadsInteroperability Instructional Videos Troubleshooting, Guides & FAQs Contact Technical Support
Resources
Product Resources by Type BattlecardBenchmarkFAQLogo & GuidelinesManualPresentationProduct BrochureProduct PhotoReference GuideRelated SolutionSales BriefSoftwareSolution BriefSolution Brief for ITSolution Brief for M&ESuccess StoryTech BriefTech BulletinTech SpecsTroubleshooting GuidesUse CaseVideoWebinarWhite Paper
Product Resources by Product Cables & AccessoriesFibre Channel HBAsSAS/SATA HBAsSAS/SATA RAID Adapters10GbE NICs25/40/50/100GbE NICs40GbE NICs
FibreBridge intelligent BridgesSiliconDisk™ RAM-based Storage ApplianceSoftwareThunderLink® - Thunderbolt™ AdaptersXstreamCORE Ethernet intelligent BridgesXstreamCORE Fibre Channel intelligent BridgesOther
Partner Resource Center
Corporate About ATTOCareersSubscribe News Events Trademark Info Privacy Policy Software Terms ROHS and Prop 65 ISO 9001 Certificate Contact Us Article Archive
ATTO Store My Account Search
Products
XstreamCORE® Storage ConnectivityXstreamCORE® intelligent BridgesXstreamCORE® JBOF ControllersSiliconDisk™ RAM-based Storage ApplianceEthernet NICsFibre Channel HBAsSAS/SATA HBAsThunderbolt™ AdaptersSoftwareXtend SAN iSCSI InitiatorDisk Benchmark for WindowsDisk Benchmark for macOS®ATTO 360 Tuning Software
ATTO Exclusive TechnologiesAdaptive Path OptimizationAdvanced Data Streaming™ATTO ConfigTool™ATTO XstreamVIEW™CacheAssure™DriveAssure™eCORE™ Control Engineintelligent Bridging Architecture™MultiPath Director™vConfigTool™xCORE™ Data Acceleration
Solutions
How to Buy
Find a Reseller United States Canada Europe, Middle East & Africa Asia / Pacific South America & Latin America
Become a Reseller
Find a Distributor United States Canada Europe, Middle East & Africa Asia / Pacific South America & Latin America
Buy Direct (ATTO Store)
Partners
Support
Sales Support Contact ATTO SalesWarranty InformationRegister a ProductAuthorize SoftwareRe-Authorize SoftwareCable FinderDiscontinued Products
Technical SupportDownloadsInteroperability Instructional Videos Troubleshooting, Guides & FAQs Contact Technical Support
Resources
Product Resources by Type BattlecardBenchmarkFAQLogo & GuidelinesManualPresentationProduct BrochureProduct PhotoReference GuideRelated SolutionSales BriefSoftwareSolution BriefSolution Brief for ITSolution Brief for M&ESuccess StoryTech BriefTech BulletinTech SpecsTroubleshooting GuidesUse CaseVideoWebinarWhite Paper
Product Resources by Product Cables & AccessoriesFibre Channel HBAsSAS/SATA HBAsSAS/SATA RAID Adapters10GbE NICs25/40/50/100GbE NICs40GbE NICs
FibreBridge intelligent BridgesSiliconDisk™ RAM-based Storage ApplianceSoftwareThunderLink® - Thunderbolt™ AdaptersXstreamCORE Ethernet intelligent BridgesXstreamCORE Fibre Channel intelligent BridgesOther
Partner Resource Center
Corporate About ATTOCareersSubscribe News Events Trademark Info Privacy Policy Software Terms ROHS and Prop 65 ISO 9001 Certificate Contact Us Article Archive
ATTO Store My Account Search
BUY
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy PolicyATTO Technology is committed to protect the privacy of the personal
information of our website visitors. This Privacy Statement explains	the guidelines we follow to protect the information you provide during
visits to our website.Personal InformationATTO
Technology will not collect personally identifiable information from you unless you knowingly and willingly agree to provide it.	Certain areas
of our website, ask for personal information, such as your name,
address, telephone number, and e-mail address.	This information is
necessary to provide customer service and process requests for technical support and product information.	Occasionally, we may request your
participation in surveys or contests for which we may require personal
information.	Your participation is totally optional and voluntary.Use of Data CollectedWe may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a
purchase, sign up for our newsletter,	respond to a survey or marketing
communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in
the following ways:To personalize user's experience and to
allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which
you are most interestedTo improve our website in order to better serve youTo allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requestsTo administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureTo send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and servicesAdvertisingThird party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet. We use interest-based advertising to serve ads that are	relevant to
you. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads
based on a user's prior visits to our website. Users may	opt out of
Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. Also	you may opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.Your OptionsWe provide the option of receiving a variety of information related to our products and services. You can subscribe to and receive	certain ATTO
Technology communications regarding new products, product updates,
product offers or promotions, or market research. We will	provide you
with the opportunity to "opt-out" of receiving communications that are
sent to you by ATTO Technology by selecting the	"opt-out" or
"unsubscribe" link, or following the "opt-out" instructions that
accompany each communication.CookiesWebsites utilize diverse technologies, such as cookies, to provide visitors a customized experience when they visit a particular site.	Cookies are data files
sent to your computer that are stored in your hard drive containing your information.	This website may utilize cookies during your visits.
Information obtained from cookies will be used only to customize your
visit and not for any other purpose.	You can set your browser to inform
you when you receive cookies or to refuse them. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser,	you can still access most of our website
areas.Web OrdersATTO’s webstore is hosted and
designed to provide a solid and secure customer experience. If you
purchase a product or service from our web store, we request certain
personally identifiable information such as name, email, and shipping
address in addition to financial information such as credit card number
and expiration date. We use this information only for billing purposes
and to fulfill orders. Should there be difficulty processing an order,
we may use this information to contact you. All credit card information
is available only to ATTO’s accounting department, processed with strict confidentiality and stored securely.Information Security and QualityATTO Technology takes precautions to protect the quality, security, and
accuracy of the information you provide on its website based on
recognized industry standards.The security of your personal
information is important to us.	When you enter sensitive information
(such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms,	we
encrypt that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology.We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal
information submitted to us,	both during transmission and once we
receive it. No method of internet transmission or electronic storage is
100% secure.	We use commercially acceptable means to protect your
personal information; however, we cannot guarantee its absolute
security.Business RelationshipsOur website may
occasionally contain links to other websites. A visitor may have
accessed our website by following a link from another	website. ATTO
Technology is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.
This privacy statement applies only to information	gathered on our
website.Updating InformationShould you need to update your personal information or remove your name from our database, please contact us.Should we revise the terms of ATTO Technology's online Privacy Policy, the revision date will be included in this document.Children's PrivacyWe do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the
age of 13. If we learn that we have the personal information of a child
under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.
We encourage parents to teach their children to never divulge personal
information unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult.ContactIf you have any questions concerning this privacy statement in particular or this website in general, please contact us.The security of your personal information is important to us. When you
enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on	our
registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure
socket layer (SSL) technology.We follow generally accepted
industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us,
both during transmission and once	we receive it. No method of internet
transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure. We use commercially
acceptable means to protect	your personal information; however, we
cannot guarantee its absolute security.Revised: 05/24/2018TopWebsite Feedbackx
Email: (optional)
Comments:
Comments can't be left blank.
Submit
Your feedback is important to us.
